Congratulations, combining LIDAR and RADAR measurements with the help of
恭喜你！利用扩展和无损卡尔曼滤波器
extended and unscented Kalman filters is incredibly impressive.
把激光雷达和雷达测量值融合到一起 是了不起的成就
These are core skills that we use on the Sensor Fusion team at Mercedes-Benz.
这是我们在梅赛德斯-奔驰的传感器融合团队的核心方法
&gt;&gt; Let's think about where Sensor Fusion fits into the entire autonomous vehicle
- 我们考虑一下 传感器融合是如何融入整个无人驾驶车
technology stack.
技术栈的
First, sensors record the data, then there are pre-processing steps such as
首先 传感器记录数据 接下来是预处理步骤
clustering algorithms, or more complex solutions to detect object hypothesis.
如使用聚类算法或更复杂的方案来检测对象假设
And finally, we can use these hypotheses as input for object level fusion.
最后 我们可以把这些假设作为对象级别融合的输入
&gt;&gt; Inside the sensor fusion block,
- 在传感器融合模块中
we combined that data together like you did in this lesson.
我们把所有数据整合到了一起 就像你在本课中做的一样
And this is not the only possible flow,
这并不是唯一的实现流程
we can apply sensor fusion at each of these processing steps.
每个处理步骤中都可以应用传感器融合
&gt;&gt; Once we have the more consistent representation of the surrounding world,
- 保证了对周围世界的一致表述后
we pass the results to other part of the autonomous vehicle system Further
我们就可以把结果传递给无人驾驶车系统的
down the line, different teams will use this data to localize the vehicle,
下游环节 不同团队可以使用这些数据来定位车辆
control the vehicle, and plan the vehicle's path.
控制车辆以及规划车辆路径
&gt;&gt; It's also worth thinking about ways in which the world is more complicated
- 我们还需要考虑 真实世界和我们
that what we've discussed so far.
目前所学内容有哪些不同之处
For example, in this lesson,
例如 在本课中
we have assumed there is only one object to track.
我们假设只追踪一个对象
But what if there are many cars on the street?
但如果街道上有多个对象呢？
Then you have to find out which measurement belongs to which vehicle,
这时候你必须确定每个测量值和具体车辆的对应关系
that makes sensor fusion even harder.
传感器融合会更加困难
&gt;&gt; But the core techniques you have learned in this lesson are the key to
- 但是 你在本课中学到的核心方法是
extended the sensor fusion block to handle these more complex scenarios.
处理这些复杂场景所需的扩展传感器融合模块的关键所在
&gt;&gt; Sensor fusion is a critical part of an autonomous driving system and
- 传感器融合是无人驾驶车系统关键部分
the other parts of the system rely on this data.
系统的其他部分都依赖于这部分的数据
&gt;&gt; In future modules, you will learn about how the components of this system
-  在后面的模块里 你会了解无人驾驶车系统
used fused sensor data to complete their functions.
的其他部分是如何使用传感器数据实现具体功能的
Good luck on the final sensor fusion project.
下面是最后一个传感器融合实战项目 祝你好运！